sweepstakesalerts.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy

**Policy Last Revised: 2017 December 21**

SweepstakesAlerts.com ("Company" "we" or "our") is committed to advising you of the right to your privacy, and strives to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, store and use personal information, provided by you on our website. By accessing and using our website, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Policy carefully, as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information, please do not use this website. 

**1. _Information You Provide and We Collect_**

We collect general types of information about you when you visit and use our website; examples include personal information, demographic information, behavioral information, and indirect information. Sometimes we collect combinations of these types of information. 

1.1. “Personal information” is information that can be used to identify you or any other individual to whom the information may relate. This is information which you are prompted to provide to us. Such information may include your name, address, telephone number(s), mobile numbers and email address, credit card number(s), bank account(s), or other unique information about you which you provide to us during the registration process, or though the course of communicating with us about the products and services provided on our website. We may collect this same information about all other persons when you provide it to us. 

1.2. “Demographic information” is information that may or may not be unique to you in the sense that it refers to selected population characteristics. Such information may include, but is not limited to, zip code, mobile phone carrier, age, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests. 

1.3. “Behavioral information” is information which is automatically collected pertaining to how you use our website, the areas of our website that you visit, what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software, including your IP address, geographic location, browser preference, operating system type, domain names, times that you access the internet, and other websites you have visited. 

1.4. “Third party information” is information about you that we acquire from a third party which may include personal, demographic, behavioral and indirect information. This collection may include, but not limited to, first party cookies, third party cookies, anonymous cookies, persistent identifiers, email opt in, and search engine keywords. We have no access or control over these cookies and other tracking devices used by third party advertisers and networks. We have no responsibility or liability for the policies and practices of these parties. 

1.5. “Web technology information” is information we automatically collect from you when you visit our website. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. This information is collected from the use of cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, local storage, and other similar mechanisms to automatically collect information. 

1.6. _No Information Collected from Children._ We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. 

**2. _Collection of Information by Web Technologies._ **

2.1 Generally, we as well as third party vendors and supporting advertisers use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, local storage and similar mechanism to automatically collect information when you visit and use our website. These technologies collect internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. This information is used to analyze trends, administer our website, track a user’s movements through our website and gather demographic information about our entire user base. We may receive reports based on these technologies on an individual or aggregated basis. 

(i) _Cookies._ “Cookies” are a feature in your browser software. If enabled, cookies store small amounts of data on your computer about actions you take on the pages of our website. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you visit most often, and what content you viewed on past visits. When you visit this website again, cookies allow us to remember you’re your settings and may be used for authentication. We may use cookies to keep track of the number of return visits, accumulate and aggregate statistical information generally pertaining to our website, and deliver specific content to you based on your past viewing history. You can disable cookies, although our website may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at [http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). In order to use all of the features and functionality of our website, you need to accept cookies. 

(ii) _Third Party Cookies._ We allow third party vendors and advertisers to set their own cookies on and through our website. We have no control over the practices of those third parties and are not responsible for their technology or tracking. We encourage you to review the policies of such persons or entities on their websites. We use AdWords Remarketing through Google which is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity on our website with the AdWords advertising network and the DoubleClick cookie. That Cookie collects information regarding certain patterns in your browsing history. To opt-out of this tracking, please see <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>. We also participate in all of Google Analytics Advertising. This includes (i) Remarketing with Google Analytics; (ii) Google Display Network Impression Reporting; (iii) DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration; and (iv) Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Google uses cookies to track activity performed by Google Analytics and its AdWords or DoubleClick cookie. To opt-out please see <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>. We also use Google Analytics which is an analysis service also provided by Google Inc. Google utilizes the data collected through its cookies to track and examine the use of this site, to prepare reports on its activities, and to share them with other Google services. You may opt-out of the Google Analytics service using Google’s Browser Add-available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>. 

(iii) _Social Media Cookies._ : Our website includes social media features. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

2.2. _Web Beacons._ We use electronic images known as Web Beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) which allow us to collect information about your visit to our website, measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements and track delivery of advertising. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view, as well as a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. We may also use Web beacons in email messages sent to you. This allows us to determine if you opened or acted upon the email messages. Because Web beacons are the same as any other content request, you cannot opt out or refuse them. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser. 

2.3. _Social Media Sharing._ You may be given the opportunity to register with us via third party accounts such as Facebook. These services will authenticate your identity and may provide you the option to share certain information (such as your name and email address) with us. We may store the information you provide us through such accounts and combine it with other information, including Personal Information. Disabling your Facebook or other such account may not terminate your account with us. Our services may also include social media features, such as sharing widgets provided by Facebook, Twitter, Google and Pinterest. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them. 

**3. _How We Use Information Collected._ **

3.1. _Providing Services and Products._ We use the information we gather on our website to provide you with the services and or products you have requested. This may include passing your information on to a third party to provide such services or products. We do not control the privacy practices of these third parties. If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from the third party databases, you will need to contact that party directly. 

3.2. _Improving Our Website._ We use the information we gather to respond to any inquires you make, operate and improve the functionality of our website, and deliver the products and services advertised on our website. Our services include the display of personalized products, content, and advertising, relating to your experience and interests. In addition, we use this information to comply with all legal obligations and resolve any disputes or concerns you may have. 

3.3 _Marketing._ We also use the information you provide to us to send you advertisements, promotions and content by third parties that we think will be of interest to you. To provide this service we may anonymize and aggregate information for different purposes which include traffic flow, analysis usage, product development, market analysis, reports and other insights. 

**4. _Disclosure of Information to Others._**

4.1. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. 

(i.) _Product and Service Delivery._ We share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of the products and services you have requested. 

(ii.) _Website Functionality._ We share your information with companies and individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf. Examples include third parties who host our website, analyze our data, provide marketing assistance, process credit card payments, and provide customer service. 

(iii) _Third Party Products and Services._ We share your information with third parties who will provide you with their opportunities, products or services. This includes your personal and non-personal information, and includes your interests and preferences, so they may determine whether you might be interested in their products or services. 

Our partners may link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt out, please visit [https://aboutads.info/choices](https://aboutads.info/choices/). 

(iv.) _Anonymous information._ We share aggregated anonymous information about you, combined with other persons using our website with third parties, so that they can understand the kinds of visitors that come to our website, and how those visitors use our website. This includes demographic information and behavioral information. 

(v.) _Legal Process._ We disclose your information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion, pursuant to a request from a governmental entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property, or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

(vi.) _Acquisition or Merger._ We may disclose and transfer your information to a third party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of, such information in a transaction approved by the court. 

**5. _Third Party Collection and Use of Information._**

5.1. Third parties collect and use information about you on or through our website in the following way: 

(i) _Advertisers._ Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place ads on our website, may use their own cookies, Web beacons, and other technology, to collect information about you. We do not control the use of such technology and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you. 

(ii) _Hyperlinks._ Our website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to websites owned by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. These links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control any information, software, products or services, available on these third party websites. The inclusion of a link on our website does not imply any endorsement of the services, products or website, or its sponsoring organization. 

(iii) _Analytics._ As described above, we use third parties to monitor analyze and report on the traffic to, from and within our website and email messages. 

**6. _Security._**

We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information. When you submit information on our website, such information is protected both online and offline. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. The servers in which we store your information are kept in a secure physical environment. The servers have industry standard firewalls. Access to such servers is password protected and access by our employees is limited. Currently, we use Secure Socket Layer software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information including credit card number(s), and names and addresses, as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although we take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure; therefore, we cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our website is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited and not accessible to the public.

**7. _Changes to Privacy Policy._**

We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Policy. We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the website, so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. 

**8. _Your California Rights._**

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the personal information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this information, please submit a written request to us at 228 Park Ave S Suite #77649, New York, NY 10003-1502. In your request, please specify that you want a “Your California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response. In addition, California residents have the right to know if we respond to do not track signals or cookies. We do not respond to such signals or cookies.

CONTACT US   
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact:  
Sweepstakes Alerts.com  
8605 Santa Monica Blvd #77649  
Los Angeles, CA 90069-4109  
(424) 772-3508
